it started as an ordinary day but for
Mrs Sharma it turned into a fight for
his husband's life diagnosed with aortic
valve stenosis Mr Sharma needed
immediate surgery to save his life the
cost was steep 20 lak rupes for the
procedure with her husband's health
insurance covering the cost she approved
the operation but complications during
surgery increased his Hospital stay and
pushed the total cost to R's 30 laks
with traditional health insurance capped
at 20 lock rupees the Sharma family
faced a daunting 10 lock rupees gap an
overwhelming financial burden during an
already stressful time thankfully they
had ICICI Lombard's Elevate health
insurance with its unlimited Su insured
feature every single expense 30 lock
rupes was fully covered free from
Financial stress Mr Sharma focused on
What mattered most his recovery and his
family because life is unpredictable but
your health insurance shouldn't be with
ICICI Lombard's Elevate health insurance
you're always covered